Guide to the Murray Webb Latimer papers, 1930-1980 MS2082
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Papers, 1930-1980; MS2082 Series 1; 39.5 Linear feet
  - NEW YORK STATE: -Service Table for Death--Benefits Census General Remarriage-Sup-lemental Social Security for Widows, undated (Box 60, Folder 6)
    Original numbering system:L524.3
  - NEW YORK STATE: -Death Study Summaries, undated (Box 60, Folder 7)
    Original numbering system:L524.4
  - Papers, undated (Box 61)
  - AMERICAN PSYCHIATRIC ASSOCIATION:-Letters to/from Dr. Chester Trent, undated (Box 61, Folder 1)
    Original numbering system:L525
  - AMERICAN PSYCHIATRIC ASSOCIATION: -Letters to Mr. Mitchell Hutchinson, undated (Box 61, Folder 2)
    Original numbering system:L525.1
  - AMERICAN PSYCHIATRIC ASSOCIATION: -Correspondence and Memoranda,Professional Society Insurance, From Mr. Mitchell Hutchinson, undated (Box 61, Folder 3)
    Original numbering system:L525.2
  - AMERICAN PSYCHIATRIC ASSOCIATION: -MISCL Correspondence and Memoranda, undated (Box 61, Folder 4)
    Original numbering system:L525.3
  - AMERICAN PSYCHIATRIC ASSOCIATION: -Insurance Co. Proposal For Member's Insurance, undated (Box 61, Folder 5)
    Original numbering system:L525.4
  - AMERICAN PSYCHIATRIC ASSOCIATION: Common Member Insurance & Retirement Plans, undated (Box 61, Folder 6)
    Original numbering system:L525.5A
  - AMERICAN PSYCHIATRIC ASSOCIATION: -Insurance and Annuity Programs for Members, undated (Box 61, Folder 7)
    Original numbering system:L525. 5B
  - AMERICAN PSYCHIATRIC ASSOCIATION: -Staff Pension Plan, 1968-1970 (Box 61, Folder 8)
    Original numbering system:L525.6
  - AMERICAN PSYCHIATRIC ASSOCIATION: -Staff Pension Plan, 1970 (Box 61, Folder 9)
    Original numbering system:L525.6a
  - AMERICAN PSYCHIATRIC ASSOCIATION: -Actuarial Variations From 1971 (Box 61, Folder 10)
    Original numbering system:L525.6b
  - Papers, undated (Box 62)
  - AMERICAN PSYCHIATRIC ASSOCIATION: -Committee on Retirement Plans, undated (Box 62, Folder 1)
    Original numbering system:L525.7
  - AMERICAN PSYCHIATRIC ASSOCIATION: -Selection of New Insurance Broker, undated (Box 62, Folder 2)
    Original numbering system:L525.8
  - AMERICAN PSYCHIATRIC ASSOCIATION: -Group Insurance Trust(l st National Bankof Minneapolis; Trustee, undated (Box 62, Folder 3)
    Original numbering system:L525.9
  - AMERICAN PSYCHIATRIC ASSOCIATION: -Prudential Contracs and Related Correspondence, undated (Box 62, Folder 4)
    Original numbering system:L525.b
  - AMERICAN PSYCHIATRIC ASSOCIATION: -Mutual of Omaha Insurance, undated (Box 62, Folder 5)
    Original numbering system:L525.11
  - AMERICAN PSYCHIATRIC ASSOCIATION: -General Association Liability Insurance, undated (Box 62, Folder 6)
    Original numbering system:L525.12
  - Papers, undated (Box 63)
  - AMERICAN PSYCHIATRIC ASSOCIATION: - Professional Liability and Malpractce [Malpractice], 1967-1974 (Box 63, Folder 1)
    Original numbering system:L525.13A
  - AMERICAN PSYCHIATRIC ASSOCIATION: - Professional Liability and Malpractce [Malpractice], 1975-1976 (Box 63, Folder 2)
    Original numbering system:L525.13B
  - AMERICAN PSYCHIATRIC ASSOCIATION: - Professional Liability and Malpractce [Malpractice], 1977 (Box 63, Folder 3)
    Original numbering system:L525.13C
  - AMERICAN PSYCHIATRIC ASSOCIATION: - Professional Liability and Malpractce [Malpractice], 1978 (Box 63, Folder 4)
    Original numbering system:L525.13D
  - AMERICAN PSYCHIATRIC ASSOCIATION: - Professional Liability and Malpractce [Malpractice]-Travel Accident Insurance, undated (Box 63, Folder 5)
    Original numbering system:L525.14
  - AMERICAN PSYCHIATRIC ASSOCIATION: - Professional Liability and Malpractce [Malpractice] -Office Building Policy, undated (Box 63, Folder 6)
    Original numbering system:L525.15
  - AMERICAN PSYCHIATRIC ASSOCIATION: - Professional Liability and Malpractce [Malpractice]-Southern California Psychiatric Society, undated (Box 63, Folder 7)
    Original numbering system:L525.16
  - AMERICAN PSYCHIATRIC ASSOCIATION: - Professional Liability and Malpractce [Malpractice]-Insurance Contract and Correspondence, Mutual Life Insurance Co. of New York (M.O.N.Y), undated (Box 63, Folder 8)
    Original numbering system:L525.17
  - Papers, undated (Box 64)
  - AMERICAN PSYCHIATRIC ASSOCIATION: -Member Retirement Plans, M.O.N.Y-Correspondence, undated (Box 64, Folder 1)
    Original numbering system:L525.18
  - AMERICAN PSYCHIATRIC ASSOCIATION: -Member Retirement Plans, M.O.N.Y-TSA Plan, undated (Box 64, Folder 2)
  - AMERICAN PSYCHIATRIC ASSOCIATION: -Member Retirement Plans, M.O.N.Y-Contracts, undated (Box 64, Folder 3)
    Original numbering system:L525.18a
  - AMERICAN PSYCHIATRIC ASSOCIATION: -Member Retirement Plans, M.O.N.Y-Final Draft, undated (Box 64, Folder 4)
    Original numbering system:L52 5. 18b
  - AMERICAN PSYCHIATRIC ASSOCIATION: -Suter Associates, undated (Box 64, Folder 5)
    Original numbering system:L525.19
  - AMERICAN PSYCHIATRIC ASSOCIATION: -Tax Deferred annuity Program, undated (Box 64, Folder 6)
    Original numbering system:L525.20
  - AMERICAN PSYCHIATRIC ASSOCIATION: -Disability Insurance Program, 1967-1974 (Box 64, Folder 7)
    Original numbering system:L525.21. 1
  - AMERICAN PSYCHIATRIC ASSOCIATION: -Disability Insurance Program, 1975 (Box 64, Folder 8)
    Original numbering system:L525.21.2
  - Papers, undated (Box 65)
  - AMERICAN PSYCHIATRIC ASSOCIATION: -Investment Results Comperisons, undated (Box 65, Folder 1)
    Original numbering system:L525.22
  - AMERICAN PSYCHIATRIC ASSOCIATION: -Complaints about Insurance, undated (Box 65, Folder 2)
    Original numbering system:L525. 23
  - AMERICAN PSYCHIATRIC ASSOCIATION: -Administration Contract, undated (Box 65, Folder 3)
    Original numbering system:L525.24
  - AMERICAN PSYCHIATRIC ASSOCIATION: -Member Retirement Plan Insurance Company Proposals, 1975-1976 (Box 65, Folder 4)
    Original numbering system:L525.25
  - AMERICAN PSYCHIATRIC ASSOCIATION: -Resumes for Position of Director,Office of Member Benefits, undated (Box 65, Folder 5)
    Original numbering system:L525.25a
  - AMERICAN PSYCHIATRIC ASSOCIATION: -Miscl., undated (Box 65, Folder 6)
    Original numbering system:L525.26
  - Papers, undated (Box 66)
  - University of Maryland-Tax Shelterd Annuities, undated (Box 66, Folder 1)
    Original numbering system:L526
  - Federal Savings and Loan Corp., undated (Box 66, Folder 2)
    Original numbering system:L527
  - PRINCE GEORGES COUNTY: -Board of Education Insurance Program, undated (Box 66, Folder 3)
    Original numbering system:L528.1
  - PRINCE GEORGES COUNTY: -County and Bd. of Education, Specifications and Invitations to Bid, undated (Box 66, Folder 4)
    Original numbering system:L528.2
  - PRINCE GEORGES COUNTY: -Censuses and Salary Data(1965) (Box 66, Folder 5)
    Original numbering system:L528. 3
  - PRINCE GEORGES COUNTY: -Group Hospital and Medical Service D.C. Proposals, undated (Box 66, Folder 6)
    Original numbering system:L528.4
  - PRINCE GEORGES COUNTY: -County and Bd. of Education Retirement Systems Study, undated (Box 66, Folder 7)
    Original numbering system:L528.5
  - AMERICAN INSTITUTE OF FREE LABOR DEVELOPEMENT(A.I.F.L.C.) AND AFRICAN AMERICAN LABOR CENTER (A.A.L.C.): -Correspondence, undated (Box 66, Folder 8)
    Original numbering system:L529
  - AMERICAN INSTITUTE OF FREE LABOR DEVELOPEMENT(A.I.F.L.C.) AND AFRICAN AMERICAN LABOR CENTER (A.A.L.C.): -Worksheets, undated (Box 66, Folder 9)
    Original numbering system:L529.1
  - AMERICAN INSTITUTE OF FREE LABOR DEVELOPEMENT(A.I.F.L.C.) AND AFRICAN AMERICAN LABOR CENTER (A.A.L.C.): -Valuation- -AIFLD-AALC, 1972 November 30 (Box 66, Folder 10)
    Original numbering system:L529.2
  - AMERICAN INSTITUTE OF FREE LABOR DEVELOPEMENT(A.I.F.L.C.) AND AFRICAN AMERICAN LABOR CENTER (A.A.L.C.): -AIFLD-AALC Pension Plan, undated (Box 66, Folder 11)
    Original numbering system:L529.2A
  - COMMUNICATIONS WORKERS OF AMERICA: -Bell System Pension Plan, undated (Box 66, Folder 12)
    Original numbering system:L531
  - COMMUNICATIONS WORKERS OF AMERICA: --Censuses-Western Electric and Bell, undated (Box 66, Folder 13)
    Original numbering system:L531.2
  - Papers, undated (Box 67)
  - COMMUNICATIONS WORKERS OF AMERICA: -Actuarial Reports AT&T Material, undated (Box 67, Folder 1)
    Original numbering system:L531.3
  - COMMUNICATIONS WORKERS OF AMERICA: -Miscl.,:AT&T Material, undated (Box 67, Folder 2)
    Original numbering system:L53.6
  - PHILADELPHIA ORCHESTRA ASSOCIATION: -Pension Report, undated (Box 67, Folder 3)
    Original numbering system:L532
  - PHILADELPHIA ORCHESTRA ASSOCIATION: -Pension Material, Report, 1962 (Box 67, Folder 4)
    Original numbering system:L532.1
  - PHILADELPHIA ORCHESTRA ASSOCIATION: -Pension Documents, undated (Box 67, Folder 5)
    Original numbering system:L532.2
  - PHILADELPHIA ORCHESTRA ASSOCIATION: -Pension Study, 1964 (Box 67, Folder 6)
    Original numbering system:L532.3
  - San Jose Newspaper Guild(Norhwest Publications, Inc., undated (Box 67, Folder 7)
    Original numbering system:L533
  - Los Angeles Newspaper Guild, undated (Box 67, Folder 8)
    Original numbering system:L534
  - Kurt Salmon Association, Inc, undated (Box 67, Folder 9)
  - DEFENSE CONTRACT AUDIT AGENCY AND ADMINISTRATIVE SERVICES: Miscl., undated (Box 67, Folder 10)
    Original numbering system:L536
  - DEFENSE CONTRACT AUDIT AGENCY AND ADMINISTRATIVE SERVICES: -Contract Payments, 1972 (Box 67, Folder 11)
    Original numbering system:L536.1
  - DEFENSE CONTRACT AUDIT AGENCY AND ADMINISTRATIVE SERVICES: -Pension Plan, Battelle Memorial Institute, undated (Box 67, Folder 12)
    Original numbering system:L536.2
  - Papers, undated (Box 68)
  - DEFENSE CONTRACT AUDIT AGENCY AND ADMINISTRATIVE SERVICES: -Sanders Associates, undated (Box 68, Folder 1)
    Original numbering system:L536.3
  - DEFENSE CONTRACT AUDIT AGENCY AND ADMINISTRATIVE SERVICES: -Sanders Associates, undated (Box 68, Folder 2)
    Original numbering system:L536.4
  - DEFENSE CONTRACT AUDIT AGENCY AND ADMINISTRATIVE SERVICES: -Emerison Electric, Chicago, undated (Box 68, Folder 3)
    Original numbering system:L536.5
  - DEFENSE CONTRACT AUDIT AGENCY AND ADMINISTRATIVE SERVICES: -Emerison Electric, chicago, undated (Box 68, Folder 4)
    Original numbering system:L536.6
  - DEFENSE CONTRACT AUDIT AGENCY AND ADMINISTRATIVE SERVICES: -McDonnell Douglas, undated (Box 68, Folder 5)
    Original numbering system:L536.7
  - DEFENSE CONTRACT AUDIT AGENCY AND ADMINISTRATIVE SERVICES: -Chrysler Appeal-Hearing, undated (Box 68, Folder 6)
    Original numbering system:L536.8
  - DEFENSE CONTRACT AUDIT AGENCY AND ADMINISTRATIVE SERVICES: -Bellcomm NASA Western Electric Dispute-Bellcomm Pension Plan Cost, undated (Box 68, Folder 7)
    Original numbering system:L536.9
  - DEFENSE CONTRACT AUDIT AGENCY AND ADMINISTRATIVE SERVICES: -Bellcomm NASA Western Electric Dispute-NASA/Western Electric, undated (Box 68, Folder 8)
    Original numbering system:L536.11
  - DEFENSE CONTRACT AUDIT AGENCY AND ADMINISTRATIVE SERVICES: -Bellcomm NASA Western Electric Dispute, 1976 (Box 68, Folder 9)
    Original numbering system:L536.12
  - DEFENSE CONTRACT AUDIT AGENCY AND ADMINISTRATIVE SERVICES: -Bellcomm NASA Western Electric Dispute-NASA-Worksheets, undated (Box 68, Folder 10)
    Original numbering system:L536.13
  - DEFENSE CONTRACT AUDIT AGENCY AND ADMINISTRATIVE SERVICES: -Bellcomm NASA Western Electric Dispute-Nasa/Western electric, undated (Box 68, Folder 11)
    Original numbering system:L536.14
  - DEFENSE CONTRACT AUDIT AGENCY AND ADMINISTRATIVE SERVICES: -Bellcomm NASA Western Electric Dispute-NASA/Western Electric, undated (Box 68, Folder 12)
    Original numbering system:L536.15
  - DEFENSE CONTRACT AUDIT AGENCY AND ADMINISTRATIVE SERVICES: -Bellcomm NASA Western Electric Dispute-Bendix, undated (Box 68, Folder 13)
    Original numbering system:L536.16
  - DEFENSE CONTRACT AUDIT AGENCY AND ADMINISTRATIVE SERVICES: -Bellcomm NASA Western Electric Dispute-General Electric, undated (Box 68, Folder 14)
    Original numbering system:L536.17
  - DEFENSE CONTRACT AUDIT AGENCY AND ADMINISTRATIVE SERVICES: -Bellcomm NASA Western Electric Dispute-General Electric, undated (Box 68, Folder 15)
    Original numbering system:L536.18
  - Papers, undated (Box 69)
  - Libbey-Owens-Ford Glass Company, 1971 (Box 69, Folder 1)
    Original numbering system:L537
  - American Home Products Corporation, undated (Box 69, Folder 2)
    Original numbering system:L538
  - American Hospital Association, undated (Box 69, Folder 3)
    Original numbering system:L539
  - UNITED TELEGRAPH WORKERS: -Agreement with Western Telegraph Co., 1975 (Box 69, Folder 4)
    Original numbering system:L539.1
  - UNITED TELEGRAPH WORKERS: -Western Union Booklets, undated (Box 69, Folder 5)
    Original numbering system:L539.2
  - UNITED TELEGRAPH WORKERS: -Miscl., undated (Box 69, Folder 6)
    Original numbering system:L539.3
  - Papers, undated (Box 70)
  - Maryland State Tax Sheltered Annuities, undated (Box 70, Folder 1)
    Original numbering system:L540
  - Maryland State Tax Sheltered Annuities, undated (Box 70, Folder 2)
    Original numbering system:L540.1
  - Casuality Actuarial Society,Announcements, Miscl., undated (Box 70, Folder 3)
    Original numbering system:L541
  - Fidelity Bonds, undated (Box 70, Folder 4)
    Original numbering system:L542
  - Humble Oil and Refining Co., undated (Box 70, Folder 5)
    Original numbering system:L550.1
  - Occupational Safety and Health -Act, undated (Box 70, Folder 6)
    Original numbering system:L551
  - Political Action Committee, Insurance Group Life Plan, undated (Box 70, Folder 7)
    Original numbering system:L56O.1
  - Stoneworkers Staff Insurance Coverage, undated (Box 70, Folder 8)
    Original numbering system:L561.1
  - Metropolitan Board of Trade, undated (Box 70, Folder 9)
    Original numbering system:L565
  - Equal Employment Opportunity Commission, undated (Box 70, Folder 10)
    Original numbering system:L570
  - Steel Industry Pay Board Report and Fringe Benefits, undated (Box 70, Folder 11)
    Original numbering system:L572
  - Williams Bill S.3598, undated (Box 70, Folder 12)
    Original numbering system:L574
  - Papers, undated (Box 71)
  - SOCIAL SECURITY: -Miscl., undated (Box 71, Folder 1)
    Original numbering system:L576
  - SOCIAL SECURITY: -Integration of Pensions with Soc. Sec., undated (Box 71, Folder 2)
    Original numbering system:L576.1
  - SOCIAL SECURITY: -Pension Summaries-Tables on Changes in Plans Since Social Security Act, undated (Box 71, Folder 3)
    Original numbering system:L576.2
  - SOCIAL SECURITY: -Hurd-Case-Lists of Companies w/Plans Amended since Passage of Soc. Sec. Act and Lists of Companies by Type of Amendment, undated (Box 71, Folder 4)
    Original numbering system:L576.3
  - SOCIAL SECURITY: -Hurd-Case-1929 Data on Selected Companies, undated (Box 71, Folder 5)
    Original numbering system:L576.4
  - SOCIAL SECURITY: -Hurd-Case-Tables and Footnotes on Changes in Pension Plans Resulting In Passage of the Soc. Sec. Act, undated (Box 71, Folder 6)
    Original numbering system:L576.5
  - SOCIAL SECURITY: -Hurd-Case-Coverage of Workers in U.S. Under Private Pension Plans, Data Relating to Count of Amended Plans Since Passage of Soc. Sec. Act and Those Unchanged Or Dropped, undated (Box 71, Folder 7)
    Original numbering system:L576.6
  - Building Trades Comments on Pension Reform Legislation and M.W.L. Comments, undated (Box 71, Folder 8)
    Original numbering system:L577
  - Conference Committee Print #1 "Employee Benefit Security Act of 1974", undated (Box 71, Folder 9)
    Original numbering system:L578
  - CORNING GLASS COMPANY: -Miscl., undated (Box 71, Folder 10)
    Original numbering system:L578.a
  - CORNING GLASS COMPANY: -Servive Tables; PCs for Amendments without Supplementation, 1976 December 31 (Box 71, Folder 11)
    Original numbering system:L578.1
  - CORNING GLASS COMPANY: -Valuation,U.S. Steel Mortality-6% as of 12/31/1976, 1976 December 31 (Box 71, Folder 12)
    Original numbering system:L578.2
  - CORNING GLASS COMPANY: Service Table for Amendments-with Supplement Action, undated (Box 71, Folder 13)
    Original numbering system:L578.3
  - CORNING GLASS COMPANY: Valuation,-IBM Tapes, 1976 December 31 (Box 71, Folder 14)
    Original numbering system:L578.4
  - Congressional Records, undated (Box 71, Folder 15)
    Original numbering system:L579
  - Hearings and Reports, undated (Box 71, Folder 16)
    Original numbering system:L580
  - Papers, undated (Box 72)
  - BALTIMORE COUNTY SCHOOLS: -Selection of Carrier, undated (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - BALTIMORE COUNTY SCHOOLS: -Correspondence, undated (Box 72, Folder 2)
    Original numbering system:L580.a
  - BALTIMORE COUNTY SCHOOLS: -Group Life Insurance-Group Life Ins., undated (Box 72, Folder 3)
    Original numbering system:L580.1
  - BALTIMORE COUNTY SCHOOLS: -Group Life Insurance-Invitation to Bid, undated (Box 72, Folder 4)
    Original numbering system:L580.1a
  - BALTIMORE COUNTY SCHOOLS: -Group Life Insurance-Funding for Retired Employees, undated (Box 72, Folder 5)
    Original numbering system:L580.lb
  - BALTIMORE COUNTY SCHOOLS: -Group Life Insurance-Selection of Insurer, undated (Box 72, Folder 6)
    Original numbering system:L580.1c
  - BALTIMORE COUNTY SCHOOLS: -Group Life Insurance-Health Insurance, undated (Box 72, Folder 7)
    Original numbering system:L580.2
  - BALTIMORE COUNTY SCHOOLS: -Group Life Insurance-Health Insurance, Funding Study, undated (Box 72, Folder 8)
    Original numbering system:L580.2a
  - BALTIMORE COUNTY SCHOOLS: -Group Life Insurance-Calculations, Working Papers, Act, undated (Box 72, Folder 9)
    Original numbering system:L580.3
  - BALTIMORE COUNTY SCHOOLS: -Group Life Insurance-Dental Insurance, undated (Box 72, Folder 10)
    Original numbering system:L580.4
  - BALTIMORE COUNTY SCHOOLS: -Group Life Insurance-Dental Insurance Invitation to Bid, undated (Box 72, Folder 11)
    Original numbering system:L580.4a
  - BALTIMORE COUNTY SCHOOLS: -Group Life Insurance-Dental Insurance; Plan Comparisons, Rates, undated (Box 72, Folder 12)
    Original numbering system:L580.4b
  - Papers, undated (Box 73)
  - NOTEBOOK BALTIMORE COUNTY SCHOOLS: -Balt. County-Schools Employee Insurance Plans, Proposals, undated (Box 73, Folder 1)
    Original numbering system:L580.5
  - NOTEBOOKS BALTIMORE COUNTY SCHOOLS: -Balt. County-Schools Employee Insurance Plans, Proposals, undated (Box 73, Folder 2)
  - NOTEBOOKS BALTIMORE COUNTY SCHOOLS: -Balt. County-Schools Employee Insurance Plans, Proposals, undated (Box 73, Folder 3)
  - NOTEBOOKS BALTIMORE COUNTY SCHOOLS: -Balt. County-Schools Employee Insurance Plans, Proposals, undated (Box 73, Folder 4)
  - NOTEBOOKS BALTIMORE COUNTY SCHOOLS: -Balt. County-Schools Employee Insurance Plans, Proposals, undated (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - NOTEBOOKS BALTIMORE COUNTY SCHOOLS: -Balt. County-Schools Employee Insurance Plans, Proposals, undated (Box 73, Folder 6)
  - NOTEBOOKS BALTIMORE COUNTY SCHOOLS: -Balt. County-Schools Employee Insurance Plans, Proposals, undated (Box 73, Folder 7)
  - NOTEBOOKS BALTIMORE COUNTY SCHOOLS: -Balt. County-Schools Employee Insurance Plans, Proposals, undated (Box 73, Folder 8)
  - NOTEBOOKS BALTIMORE COUNTY SCHOOLS: -Balt. County-Schools Employee Insurance Plans, Proposals, undated (Box 73, Folder 9)
  - NOTEBOOKS BALTIMORE COUNTY SCHOOLS: -Balt. County-Schools Employee Insurance Plans, Proposals, undated (Box 73, Folder 10)
  - NOTEBOOKS BALTIMORE COUNTY SCHOOLS: -Balt. County-Schools Employee Insurance Plans, Proposals, undated (Box 73, Folder 11)
  - Papers, undated (Box 74)
  - Miscl. Memoranda on Pension Reform Legislation, undated (Box 74, Folder 1)
    Original numbering system:L581
  - ASSOCIATION OF SCIENTISTS AND PROFESSIONAL ENGINEERING PERSONNEL: -Worthington Corporation, undated (Box 74, Folder 2)
    Original numbering system:L581.A
  - ASSOCIATION OF SCIENTISTS AND PROFESSIONAL ENGINEERING PERSONNEL: -Worthington Corp.,Salaried Employees Retirement Plan, undated (Box 74, Folder 3)
    Original numbering system:L581.1
  - ASSOCIATION OF SCIENTISTS AND PROFESSIONAL ENGINEERING PERSONNEL: -Worthington Corp. Interim Report, undated (Box 74, Folder 4)
    Original numbering system:L581.2
  - ASSOCIATION OF SCIENTISTS AND PROFESSIONAL ENGINEERING PERSONNEL: -A.S.P.E.P. Data, undated (Box 74, Folder 5)
    Original numbering system:L581.3
  - Insurance Workers International Union, A.F.L.-C.I.O., undated (Box 74, Folder 6)
    Original numbering system:L582
  - Pension Litigation, undated (Box 74, Folder 7)
    Original numbering system:L582.A
  - BASIC STEEL: -Pension Material, undated (Box 74, Folder 8)
    Original numbering system:L583.A
  - BASIC STEEL: -Pensions, 1965 (Box 74, Folder 9)
    Original numbering system:L583.B
  - BASIC STEEL: -Pensions, undated (Box 74, Folder 10)
    Original numbering system:L583.C
  - Cyprus, undated (Box 74, Folder 11)
    Original numbering system:L583.1
  - Papers, undated (Box 75)
  - Pension Plan Termination Insurance co. Metropolitan Life Insurance, undated (Box 75, Folder 1)
    Original numbering system:L584
  - Regulation of Employee Benefits, Plan Termination Insurance, Preliminary Staff Working Draft, undated (Box 75, Folder 2)
    Original numbering system:L585
  - Private Pension Legislation and Miscl. Bills, undated (Box 75, Folder 3)
    Original numbering system:L586
  - Register of Retirement Benefits Plans, undated (Box 75, Folder 4)
    Original numbering system:L587
  - Study of the Cost of Mandatory Vesting Provision Proposed for Private Pension Plans, undated (Box 75, Folder 5)
    Original numbering system:L588
  - Plan Termination Insurance, undated (Box 75, Folder 6)
    Original numbering system:L589
  - Plan Terminations-Recoupment of Overpayments, undated (Box 75, Folder 7)
    Original numbering system:L589.a
  - EMPLOYEE- RETIREMENT INCOME SECURITY ACT: - Employee Retire. Income. Sec. Act, undated (Box 75, Folder 8)
    Original numbering system:L590
  - EMPLOYEE- RETIREMENT INCOME SECURITY ACT: -Amendments, undated (Box 75, Folder 9)
    Original numbering system:L590.1
  - Papers, undated (Box 76)
  - EMPLOYEE- RETIREMENT INCOME SECURITY ACT: -Impraements Act of 1979 (Box 76, Folder 1)
    Original numbering system:L590.1a
  - EMPLOYEE- RETIREMENT INCOME SECURITY ACT: -Regulations, undated (Box 76, Folder 2)
    Original numbering system:L590.2
  - EMPLOYEE- RETIREMENT INCOME SECURITY ACT: -Compliance Manual, undated (Box 76, Folder 3)
    Original numbering system:L590.4
  - EMPLOYEE- RETIREMENT INCOME SECURITY ACT: -Press Releases, U.S. Dept. of Labor, Women's Bureau, undated (Box 76, Folder 4)
  - Welfare and Pension Plan Disclosure Act, undated (Box 76, Folder 5)
    Original numbering system:L591
  - PENSION BENEFIT-GUARANTY CORPORATION: -P.B.G.C., undated (Box 76, Folder 6)
    Original numbering system:L592
  - PENSION BENEFIT-GUARANTY CORPORATION: -Publications, Publicity, undated (Box 76, Folder 7)
    Original numbering system:L592.1
  - PENSION BENEFIT-GUARANTY CORPORATION: P.B.G.C. AND C.E.L.I.(Contingents Employees Liability), 1977 (Box 76, Folder 8)
    Original numbering system:L592.2
  - PENSION BENEFIT-GUARANTY CORPORATION: P.B.G.C. AND C.E.L.I., 1978 (Box 76, Folder 9)
    Original numbering system:L592.3
  - PENSION BENEFIT-GUARANTY CORPORATION: -P.B.G.C.-Multi-Employer Study, 1978 (Box 76, Folder 10)
    Original numbering system:L592.4
  - PENSION BENEFIT-GUARANTY CORPORATION: Pregnancy as Disability,Legislation (H.R. 6075), undated (Box 76, Folder 11)
    Original numbering system:L593.1
  - Papers, undated (Box 77)
  - Pregnancy as Disability-Legislation-includes General Electric vs.A.F.L.-C.I.O.-C.L.C., undated (Box 77, Folder 1)
    Original numbering system:L593.2